Guide to the Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
Ashbery, Ray Stevens papers, [1930-1971?].
- Series II. Subject files, 1948-1962. Assembly files, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Ithaca - Tuning Fork (Brainard), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Judiciary, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Jury Duty, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Justices, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Kelly, John H., 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Labor, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
  - Law Revision Commission, 1958, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
  - League of Women Voters (Legislation), 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Legislation - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - Legislation - Proposed, 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Manuals 1957-59, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Procedure 1958, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Legislature, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Liberal Party of New York State, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Libraries, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Libraries - Proposed Legislation, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Long Island Railroad Company, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Medicine, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Meetings - Friday, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Meeting - State Affairs Committee, Sept. 26, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Meetings, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Mental Retardation, JLC on (Earl Brydges), 1958 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Motor Bus, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 39-40)
  - Motor Vehicle Bureau - Licenses, 1957-58, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Municipalities, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Newfield Central School, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Charles H. Newman, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - News Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 45-47)
  - New York State Council of Retail Merchants, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - New York State Educational Conference Board, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - New York State Grange, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Northway, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Off- Track Betting, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Ophthalmology, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Optometrists, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Parks, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Payrolls, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Probe-Payrolls, Legislative, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Psychologists, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 59-60)
  - Railroads, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Red Books, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1958 Speakers, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Republican Party (State), 1958, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
  - Republican Picnic, July 12, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Republican Party (Tompkins County), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Requests for Report, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Retirement Legislation, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Retirement - Tompkins County C contribution, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Sales Tax - Tompkins County, 1957-58 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Sampson, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sheriffs' Association, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Social Security Staff, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Social Welfare - 1 Year Residency, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
  - Speech Material, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
  - Syracuse, Sept. 22, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Taber, Hon. John, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Taxes, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Teachers, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Tompkins County, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Tompkins County Board of Supervisors, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Tompkins County Extension Service - 4-Club, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Tompkins County Hospital, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Tompkins County - Ithaca Speed Control - Re-routing, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Tompkins County Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Trapp, Stella M., 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Ulysses, Town of, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Unanswered Mail, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 33-34)
  - Wiretapping, 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Wolverton, Robert S. - Batavia School for the Blind, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Women's Legislative Luncheon, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Youth, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Youth Court Act, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Adams, L. P., Extra Service Payroll Vouchers, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Adoptions - D. Lawrence, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Aging, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Agriculture, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 44-46)
  - Albany - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 47-51)
  - Albany - Desk, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Albany - Health Committee Report, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Albany Report, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Alcohol - Alcoholics and ABC Law, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Amendments - 1961-62, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - American Association of University Women, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Arts - New York State Council, ca. 1962 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Assembly, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - News Releases, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 60-62)
  - Ashbery - New York State Fair, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Ashbery - Personal, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Associated Industries, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 65-66)
  - Ashbery - Personal, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Ashbery - Stag Get-together at 40 Whig Street, Apr. 18, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Ashbery - Take Home - Mar. 17, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Associated Industries of New York State, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Association of Towns, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Development, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - New York State Automobile Association, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Banking, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Banks, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bar Association, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 7-11)
  - Barge Canal, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
  - Bills - Prefiled, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
  - Bingo, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Blue Cross Hearings - Metcalf, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Boating, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bradley, Pete - News Releases, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Brockway, Richard, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
  - Budget, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 22-24)
  - Bus Transportation to Schools, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 26-27)
  - Campaign Broadcasts - 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Carlino Letters, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Caroline Youth Camp, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Censorship, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Cerebral Palsy Four- County Drive, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Cerebral Palsy - Victory Club, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 34-36)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Friday Luncheons, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Chamber of Commerce - New York, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Champion, Arthur - drivers license, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Children, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Chiropractors, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 41-42)
  - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey, Inc., 1961 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Citizens Union, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 44-46)
  - Civil Practice Act, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Civil Practice Act Revision, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Civil Service, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 49-50)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - College Applications, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Commerce, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Commerce and Industry, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Commerce and Industry - The Legislative Hopper, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Commerce and Industry Association, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Communications, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Conference of Mayors, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 7-9)
  - Conservation, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 10-12)
  - Constitution, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Consumers, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Cook, Constance - Legislative Correspondence, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Cornell, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Morrill or Land Grant Act, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Cornell - Land Grant Centennial, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correction, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - to be answered, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
  - Council of Churches, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 24-25)
  - County Government, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - County Lawyers, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 27-28)
  - Courts, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Courts - Reorganization, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Crime, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Criminal Law, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Diefendorf Committee Report, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Drinking Bill 18-21, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 34-35)
  - Drunken Driving, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Education, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 1-9)
  - Education Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
  - Education - Finance, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Education - Higher, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Education, Ithaca board of, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Education - City of Ithaca, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Education - Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Education - Licensing, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Education - Teachers, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Elections, ca. 1960 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fall Out Nuclear War, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Fall Out Shelters, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Farm Bureau, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Farm Bureau - Broadcast, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Farm Organizations, New York State Conference Board of, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Farm Safety Legislation, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Firearms, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Firemen - Legislation re., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Freeman, Frank S. - Psychologists, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Full Crews Law, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Gambling, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General Laws Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - George Junior Republic, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Message, News Releases, etc., 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 5-8)
  - Groton Centennial, Aug. 6, 1960, 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Haight, Marlene F. - Application Health Committee, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Hane, Lana, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Healing Arts - Resolution 62, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Health Insurance - New York State, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Health Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
  - Health, Public, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Health Committee, Public, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
  - Health and Narcotics, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Highways, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
  - Highways - Route 96-227-13, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Highways - Route 96, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Highways - Route 227, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Holidays, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Home Builders Association, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Home Building, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Home Remedies, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Home Rule, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Hospital Association of New York State, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Housing, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
  - Human Slaughter, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Hypnosis, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Insurance, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 35-36)
  - Invitations, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 37-38)
  - Invitation, Meetings, Etc., 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 39-41)
  - Ithaca - City School District, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Ithaca School Board Meetings, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Judiciary, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 44-45)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Labor, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Law Revision Commission, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - League of Women Voters, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 10-11)
  - Legislative - Invitations, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Legislative - Job Applications, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Legislative - Miscellaneous, July, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Research (Room 140), 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Research, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
  - Legislative Reports, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Liberal Party, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 19-20)
  - Libraries, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Car) - Special Requests, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Liquor Law, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Mail - for answering, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Matrimonial and Family Laws, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Matrimony, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Meetings, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Mental Health Conference - Harrisburg (Sept. 28-29, 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Mental Hygiene, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Senator Metcalf - Reports, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Migrants, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Minimum Wage Law, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1956-1961 (Box 22, Folder 34-35)
  - Motor Vehicle - Registration 1962, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Newman, Charles H., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - New York, City of, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 2-4)
  - New York County Lawyer's Association, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - New York Good Roads, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - New York State - AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - New York State Automobile Association, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - New York State Banker, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - New York State Home Builders Association, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, 1959-1961 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
  - News Releases 1962 - Bradley, etc., 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Nurses, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Offensive and Obscene Material, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Office Help - Albany, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Off-Track Betting, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ophthalmologists, Optometrists, Opticians, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Passes, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
  - Pharmaceutical, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Pollution, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Port of New York Authority Meeting, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Power Resources, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Preller, Fred. W., 1961 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Prisoners, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Public Employee Amer. Fed. State, County and [?] Employees, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Department of Public Works, 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 28-29)
  - Board of Rabbis, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Railroads, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 31-33)
  - Real Property Law, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Reapportionment, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Red Books, 1957-1961 (Box 23, Folder 36-37)
  - Red Book and Legislative Manual, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Redistricting 1961-62, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Reorganization Plan (State), 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Republican Party, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Republican Party - New York State, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Republican State Committee, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Requests for bills after session, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Retail Merchants, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Retail Merchants, New York State Council of, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Rice, Adelaide, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Safety, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 48-49)
  - Sampson Park, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Savings Bank, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Scholar Incentive, $200, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Scholarship Incentive Plan, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Schools and Teachers, Inc. to, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - School Boards - Central Area H, Dryden Central, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Seaway Canal, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Shelters, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Social Security, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Speaker's Releases, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Speaker's Weekly Newsletter, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Special Session Nov. 9-10, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Speech Material, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
  - State Government, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - State University - Master Plan, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Steuben Society, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Surrogate, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Taggart - Motor Vehicle, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Taxation, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Taxes, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Teacher's Pensions 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Television, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Tompkins County Board of Supervisors, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Tompkins County - East Shore (Lieberman), 1961 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Tompkins County - Miscellaneous, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
  - Tompkins County - Unanswered mail, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 22-23)
  - Trailer Tax Assessment, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Transportation, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Trumansburg Postmaster and Post Office, 1960, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Ulster Commentary, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Uniform Commercial Code, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Vandalism, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1958-1962 (Box 24, Folder 31-32)
  - Voting, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Waterfront, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Water Resources - New York State, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Welfare - Social, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Welfare, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Welfare - Health of Aging, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Wilson, Lt. Governor Malcolm, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Wiretapping, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Wiretapping, etc., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Women, American Association of University (Women's Legislative Luncheon), 1960 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 43-44)
  - World's Fair, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Youth, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Health, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Health Committee, Public, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Highways, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Hospital Association of New York State, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Housing, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hypnosis, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Insurance, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ithaca Arterial (Route 13), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca - School District, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Judiciary, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Labor, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Law Revision C Comission, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - League of Women Voters, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Legislation, Proposed - Lansing School Transfer, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Legislation - Banks, 1961, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Legislation, 1961 - Route 13 Relocation, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Legislation, 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Legislative Research Report, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Liberal Party, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Library, 1061-1962 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Liquor, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mental Health, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Metcalf Releases, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Migrants, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Milk Dating, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Motorbuses, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Motor Vehicle, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Ashbery - First Campaign, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Assembly - 1958 Campaign, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Ashbery - Campaign, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Assembly Files - Olin Research Library, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Ashbery - Pending Matters, 1958-1962 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Index and Map of New York State Institutions and Properties, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - ABC, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Television, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Friday - Forums - Ithaca, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - M.P. File, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
  - Republican Party Notes and Releases, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Speeches, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - 1953-1955 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 1956 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Messages, 193 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - ABC, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Campaign Petitions, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Biggs Hospital, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Town of Ithaca - Equalization appeal, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Committee Report on Bills, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 21-24)
  - Biggs Hospital, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Tompkins County Hospital, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Hospital - Tompkins County Memorial to Biggs, 1955-1956 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - 1960 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - 1952, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - NOTE: Box 27 not listed or found. (Box 27)
  - Homer Browning - Marine Trust Co., Buffalo, NY [Trumansburg], 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Village Bonds and Financial Reports [Trumansburg], 1935, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - La Valley: E. C. District Sanitary Engineer [Trumansburg], 1943-1945 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - [Trumansburg], 1959, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Contracts - Andrew Well [Trumansburg], 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - [Trumansburg], n.d. (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - Bids May 10 [Trumansburg], 1945 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - [Trumansburg], 1933, 1945, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - District #3 Krums Corners, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - 57 School 3 Joel E. Taylor - Accident [Trumansburg], 1957 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - [Trumansburg], 1944-1945, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Village Board Minutes [Trumansburg], 1958-1961 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - New York State Electric and Gas Street Lighting [Trumansburg], 1961 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Pipe [Trumansburg], 1945 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - (re Andrew Well) Estimate - Petitions, etc. [Trumansburg], 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - 52 Miscellaneous 33 School Building - Correspondence with Reed, Hoyt, Taylor and Washburn [Trumansburg], 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - 52 Miscellaneous 33 School Building - Correspondence with Marine Trust company, Buffalo, New York [Trumansburg], 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - 52 Miscellaneous 33 Trumansburg Central School - New Building, 1951-1953 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - 52 Miscellaneous 33 New Elementary School Documents, 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 20-21)
  - 56 village 2 Salo Drive [Trumansburg], 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - 55 Village 5 Finn Lane - Trumansburg, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - 56 Village 3 Census - Intermediate Trumansburg, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Trumansburg, 1958-1961 (Box 28, Folder 25-27)
  - Trumansburg - Village Minutes, 1950-52, 1950-1953 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Trumansburg - Reed, Hoyt, Washburn, 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Trumansburg - Elmendorf: C.E. (Wm. S. Lozier & Co.), 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Trumansburg - 58 Village 12 Bingo, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, 1962-1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Assembly Miscellaneous to file, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Assembly - mostly Joint Legislative Committee Unemployment Ins., 1951-1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Bergholtz Tract, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Speech Material, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Ashbery Thruway Recommendations, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Tompkins Co. Bar Association - Legislative Committee, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Tompkins Co. Bar Association - Ashbery, president, 1954-1955 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Tompkins Co. Bar Association - Publications, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 14)